# **Asaf Dulman**

# Looking for a Frontend / Fullstack Position





asafdulman@gmail.com

Website

#### **Summary**

Frontend/Full-Stack Web Developer with knowledge and experience writing single-page applications, using the latest web technologies, such as React.js Node.js, Vue.js and Angular.

My latest project is **SupaLife**, a mobile app to record and measure personal memories. Made with React (Hooks), Scss, NodeJs and MongoDB.

B.A in Behavioral Sciences, people oriented, keeping the person in front of the screen in-mind when coding.

#### **Technical Skills:**

- Programing in modern JavaScript (ES6), including Object-Oriented Programing.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SCSS; PSD to a live page. Responsive design and & "Mobile First".
- MVC, React Hooks, Redux, MobX.
- Server side, APIs and REST; Node.JS.
- Using MySQL and MongoDB for database

#### **EDUCATION**

- 2020 Fullstack Bootcamp Graduate from Coding Academy.
- 2015 B.A in Behavioral Sciences Tel Aviv-Yaffo Academic College.
- 2014 Academic Diploma in Broadcasters and Sportswriters Studies Seminar HaKibbutzim College.
- **2005 Maccabim-Reut MOR Highschool –** Economics and Business Management.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### 2016 – 2021 Head of Publishers at ZipporMedia

- Managing over 80 accounts, building long-term and trustful relationships with partners. In charge of all supply side video activities.
- Ad Operations Team Manager. Creating daily processes and prioritizing tasks.
- Experienced in data analysis, recognizing industry trends and building strategies to reach both personal objectives and team goals.
- Responsible for the department's financial reporting.

## **2014 – 2016** TV Commercials Agency Producer at McCANN Tel Aviv.

- Full management of TV and digital media commercial productions. In charge of maintaining relationships with the company's high-profile clients, e.g. Tnuva, El Al, Bank Leumi, Osem and others.
- The position included leading projects around the clock in a fast paced, intensive environment, while managing tight and demanding schedules.

## 2014 Freelance Online Sports Writer for israelsport.co.il

## **MILITARY SERVICE**

# 2005- 2008 Full Combat Service in Battalion 94, Kfir Brigade – Senior Sargent

• Served as a commander for two years, one of which as a Platoon Senior Combat Sergeant (010). In charge of operation planning and executing complicated tasks in a hostile terrain.

### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS & HOBBIES**

- Sports Geek Deep knowledge and understanding of various sports fields, specializing in European Football and International Basketball.
- English Fluent, Hebrew Native language